Everyone Assemble
Fufufu... In that case, we'll
decide this with volleyball.
（古市）「フフフ…こうなったら
バレーボールで勝負だ」→
「ただし　ボールのかわりに…
これをつかってなっ！」→
But instead of a ball, we'll use... this!
「なっ　なんだって！」
…って　エエ～ッ！
W-What did you say?!
（古市）いいところで終わり～！？
And it just ends there?!
どうなるんだ！？
ボールのかわりに何を使うんだ！？
What happens next?
What will they use instead of a ball?
（古市）しまった！最新号は男鹿に
貸したままじゃねぇか～。
Crap... I lent the latest volume
to Oga, and he still has it!
もう遅いな～…
だが　このままじゃ→
It's already late.
But I won't be able to sleep
unless I know what happens next!
続きが気になって
眠れねぇぞ～。
そうだ！アランドロン！→
That's it! Alaindelon!
ちょっと
男鹿の家まで次元転送して…。
Would you dimensionally
transfer me to Oga's house...?
ひょっとして　男鹿んところから
ベル坊がいなくなって→
I wonder if he and Hilda-san also cleared
out when Baby Beel left Oga's place?
あの　おっさんもヒルダさんと
一緒に行っちまったのか…。
んっ？
（手紙：アランドロンの声）
「古市殿　私がいなくなって→
Furuichi-dono, please use this when you
just can't bear with my absence any longer.
どうしても
我慢（がまん）ができなくなった時→
これを　お使いください」。
あん？
（古市）市民プールの割引券！？→
A discount coupon for the municipal pool?!
だから　どうした～！！
What's with that?!
（男鹿）
えれ～目にあったぜ
あのラミアとかいうクソガキ…。
That was pretty horrid...
Damn that shitty brat, Lamia...
ん？
さては　また
あのラミアとかいうガキだな…。
And now it looks like that
brat Lamia's here again!
ぶっ殺すぞ　こら～っ！！
I'll kill you, you...
（城山）あっ…。
あああっ…。
ずいぶんと　変な嫌がらせ
するじゃねぇか　ラミア。
You have strange way of trying
to get rid of me, Lamia.
いや…俺　城山。
No... I'm Shiroyama.
（城山）
インターホンを押そうと
思ったんだが時間も遅いしな。→
I was going to ring the
buzzer, but it's very late.
どうしたもんかと
悩んでたら→
While I was trying to figure my next move,
I heard your voice from the bathroom.
お前の声が
風呂場からしたもんでな。
気持ちわり～ヤツだな。
You're creepy.
だいたい何の用だ？
どこに連れて行くつもりだ？
What do you want anyway?
Where are you leading me?
（城山）
神崎さんと姫川さんが待ってる。
Kanzaki-san and Himekawa-san
are waiting for you.
あん？またやろうってのか！？
They want to go at it again?
（城山）違う。東条絡みで話がある。
No.
They want to talk about Tojo.
東条…？
ああ。
Tojo?
Yeah.
（城山）実は…。
You see...
（神崎）((東条…))
（姫川）((俺達も混ぜろよ…))
Tojo...
Let's mix it up.
（東条）((ええっと…))
（陣野）((神崎と姫川))
Uh...
Kanzaki and Himekawa.
（東条）((ああ　そ～か…。
よお！神崎と…→
Oh, right.
Hey, Kanzaki and... uh,
Himekawa, right? What's up?
ええ～　姫川じゃあねぇか
何か用か？))
（姫川）
((フフッ…。相変わらずムカつく
ヤロ～だ…眼中にねぇってか))
It's like we don't even exist?
Damn, you piss me off.
（神崎）((とぼけやがって　ネタは
とっくにあがってんだよ！))
Stop playing innocent! We know all about it!
（東条）((ネタ？))
（神崎）((うちの下の者　根こそぎ
奪っていっただろうが！))
It?
You've taken all of our followers!
（東条）((知らんな))
No clue.
（陣野）((確かに…。今　石矢魔の
勢力図は激変している))
It is true that the balance of power
at Ishiyama is rapidly changing.
（東条）((そうなのか？))
Is it?
（陣野）
((ああ。この２人が男鹿に
やられてからというもの→
Yes. Since these two were beaten by Oga,
ほとんどの奴が
東条一派を自称している。→
most of the rank-and-file have proclaimed
themselves as being "with Tojo".
男鹿に勝てるのはもう　お前しか
いないと踏んだんだろう))
Perhaps they believe you're
the only one able to beat Oga.
（陣野）((だが　それは
そいつらが勝手に→
But that's simply because they
decided to give up on you two.
お前らを見限っただけの事…
俺達には関係ない))
It has nothing to do with us.
（神崎）((てめっ…！))
Why, you...
((フッ…。
まっ　なんでもいいや))
Fine, whatever.
((文句あるなら
ゲンコツでこいよ))
You got a problem with me, come and fight!
（神崎・姫川）
((上等だ　こら～っ！！))
You're on, asshole!
((虎が相手をするまでもない))
They are no opponents for you, Tora.
（神崎・姫川）((おっ…！))
（姫川）…というわけでだ。
And so, we're here.
しょ～がねぇから
てめ～も仲間に入れてやるよ。
We don't like it, but we'll let you join us.
東条　ぶっ倒しに行くぞ！
Let's go beat the crap outta Tojo.
…はっ？
Huh?
（姫川）「はっ？」じゃね～よ。
わかってんだろ？
Huh, what? You heard us!
（神崎）
俺達が　力かしてやるってんだ。
行くぞ　おら！
We told you to help us!
Now, let's go!
はっ？
Huh?
（神崎）…いいか！！
勘違いすんなよ→
Listen! Don't get the wrong idea.
てめ～も　ぶっ飛ばしてやりたい
ところだが　今は東条が先だ。
We want to beat you up,
too. But Tojo comes first!
ああ　あいつだけは　さっさと
やっちまわなけりゃならねぇ→
Yes. We have to get rid of him immediately.
ここは一時　共同戦線と
いこ～じゃね～か。
For the time being, let's
fight on the same side!
いや。別にいいです。
１人でやるし…。
Um, thanks but no thanks. I'll do it myself.
（神崎）いいか　勘違いするなよ！→
Listen! Don't get the wrong idea!
てめ～も　ぶっ飛ばしてやりたい
ところだが　今は東条が先だ！
We want to beat you up,
too! But Tojo comes first!
（姫川）
ああ…あいつだけは　さっさと
やっちまわなけりゃならねぇ→
Yes! We have to get rid of him immediately.
ここは一時　共同戦線と
いこ～じゃね～か。
For the time being, let's
fight on the same side!
くりかえし！？
They're stuck in a loop?!
すまん。本当は
お前の力を借りたいんだ。
Sorry... They want to ask for your help.
ああ　なんだそりゃ！
What the heck?
《ふざけんなよ！だったら
もっと下手にでろや！→
You've gotta be kiddin' me.
They should beg! Maybe I'll  squeeze
out where Tojo is and bury 'em.
東条の居場所
はかせて埋めたろか！→
まっ…今日のメインは東条だ》
Well, my main objective today is Tojo.
わかったよ。そんなに
来たけりゃ　一緒に来い！
Okay then. If you really
wanna come, stick with me.
ちっ　しょ～がねぇな～。
今回だけだぞ。
I'd rather not, but...
Just this once, got it?
くっ…んん…。
（東条）どうした？元気ねぇな～。
What's the matter? You don't seem well.
（ベル坊）バ～…ブ～…。
（東条）そんなんじゃ
生き残れねぇぞ。
You'll never survive like that.
（ベル坊）ダ～ブ～…。
１２歳の東条
((ハァハァハァ…))
((うっ…ハァハァハァ…))
（店主の声）
((こら待て　ドロボー！！))
((ハァハァハァ…))
Hold it right there, thief!
（東条）フッ…よし！→
Right!
こんな時は　やっぱあれだな
ドカン！と一発派手にやるか～。
Times like this, there's
only one thing to do!
We'll set things off with a big bang!
（相沢）えっ？…学校？
今からっすか…→
The school? Now?
そりゃま～別にいいっすけど…
じゃあ　またあとで。
Fine, I don't really mind, but...
Talk to you later.
はぁ～…。
んっ？
（相沢）よお！男鹿ちゃん。
Hey, Oga-chan.
どしたの　こんな時間に？
（神崎）相沢。
What're you doing here this late?
Aizawa.
（相沢）
しかも　随分と珍しい面子だね。
Plus, you've got quite
the odd group with you.
（神崎）電話の相手は東条か？
（相沢）だったらどうよ。
Was that Tojo you were
speaking to on the phone?
And what if it was?
ちょうどいい
案内してもらおうか。
Perfect. We'll have you lead us to him.
（不良）まちな。
（姫川）んっ？
Hold it!
（不良）相沢さん。ここは俺達に
まかせて下さいよ。
Aizawa-san, please leave this to us.
はぁ？
（不良）
そして　勝ったあかつきには
正式に認めてもらいますよ。→
When we win, you'll
recognize us officially...
東条さんの部下として…。
As Tojo-san's underlings!
いやいや。つ～か…誰　君達？
Uh... Who are you people?
（不良）≪ちょっと待った～！≫
あ？
Hold it!
（不良）そういうことなら
俺達も参加しますよ。→
In that case, let us join in as well!
チャンスは
平等に　いきましょ～や。
Everyone should get an equal chance!
バ～カ。
おめぇじゃ　実力不足だ。
Idiots... You don't have what it takes.
（不良）≪あ～あ？≫
≪待て待て
男鹿をやるのは俺達だ≫
Hold it, hold it! We'll
be the ones to get Oga!
≪バカ　俺に決まってんだろ≫
≪いやいや　俺！≫
≪オレオレ！≫
≪サギか　てめえは！≫
Me, me!
You're a cheat!
（不良達の騒ぐ声）
う～ん…なんだ　これ？→
The hell?
めんどくさ～　君達
今　何時だと思ってんの？→
This is gonna be annoying.
Do you know what time it is?
ご近所の迷惑も考えなさいよ。
Please think of the trouble
you're causing the neighborhood.
あっ　待て　こらっ！
Wait, you!
てめ～との
勝負はまだ　ついてね～ぞ！！
Our fight isn't over yet!
（相沢）そいつら　全員
倒したら相手してやるよ。
Beat everyone there, and I'll fight you.
きっ…。
（神崎）≪ふん≫
（神崎）みくびられたものだな。
（姫川）ああ　まったくだ。
They don't think much of us...
Yeah, seriously.
≪かかってこいや～　姫川！≫
≪どうした　神崎！≫
Bring it on, Himekawa!
What's the matter, Kanzaki?
てめえら
誰を前に息まいてんだ。
Do you realize who you're barking at?
教育が必要だな。
Looks like you need to be taught a lesson.
（不良達）わぁ～！！
♪♪～
（不良）うう…。
（姫川）ケッ。
ど～した…もう終わりか？
What? Over already?
次！
Next!
（姫川・神崎）ああ…。
何してる…行くぞ。
What're you doing? Let's go.
（姫川・神崎）お…おう。
R-Right...
…って　待て　こらっ！
Hold it, you!
（姫川）俺達　おめえの
子分じゃねぇんだぞ！
We're not your lackeys, got it?
（姫川）前　歩いてんじゃね～よ。
You shouldn't be walking in front!
《めんどくせ～…》
God, they're a pain...
（神崎）待てよ　こら～！
（姫川）男鹿～！！
Hold it, damn you!
Oga!
（ヒルダ）坊っちゃまが病に伏して
もう　まる３日→
It's been almost 3 days
since the master became ill.
こんなに　のんびりしていて
よいのでしょうか？
Do we really have time to
be taking things slowly?
（ラフマニノフ）うむ。だが焦りは禁物。→
True... But haste must be avoided.
我々が施した治療は
失われたリンクそのものを→
The cure we are pursuing is to
restore the lost link itself.
見つけ出すところまでだ。
それを実際　つなぎ直し→
The only one who can recover it...
and restore the bond... is that man.
それを修復できるのは
あの男だけ。
（ラフマニノフ）つまり　あの男が自ら
ベルゼ様を→
In other words, unless that man, of his
own will, goes to get Beelze-sama back,
取り戻しに行かなければ
意味はない。
there is no point.
（ラミア）≪フンだ！≫
（ラミア）
あんな男なんか
死んじゃえばよかったのよ！
That man should just drop dead!
ラミア…。
なんだ？
Lamia...
What? Still angry after he spanked your ass?
ケツをひっぱたかれたこと
まだ根に持っているのか。
（ラミア）知りません！
I don't know what you're talking about!
乙女にむかって
ケツとか言わないで下さい！
Don't say "ass" in front of a lady!
だいたいっ！師匠は立場上→
And besides...
You can't show favor to one prince only!
１人の王子を贔屓しちゃ
いけないんですよ～！！
すまんな…ラミア。
Sorry, Lamia.
あっ…。
Well, I like you a lot, Miss
Hilda, so I don't mind.
まっ…ヒルダお姉様のこと
好きだから別にいいけど…。
フッ…。
坊っちゃま…。
Master...
（不良）どうぞ　相沢さん
行って下さい。
Go on, Aizawa-san. Go right ahead.
Huh? Who are you people?
あら～…何なの君達？
We'll cut off their advance here!
（不良）
ここは俺達が　くいとめます。
We said not to run out in front of us!
（神崎）だから　俺の前を
走るな～ってんだろ～が。→
Hey! Hold it, Oga!
こら～　待てや～…男鹿！
Cut off their advance? Look
here, people, this isn't a war.
（姫川）くいとめるって…あのね
君達　戦争じゃないんだから。
It is a war!
（不良）戦争っすよ。
石矢魔の誇りをかけた。
A war for Ishiyama's honor.
Yeah. We can't let some
first-year walk all over us.
（不良）
そう。１年に仕切られるなんて事があっちゃならないんです。
（不良）現に　ほとんどの生徒が
今ここに集まっています。
Pretty much every student
is gathered here now.
Oookay... Well, don't overdo it.
ああそう。ま…程々にね。
Tojo-san is calling for me, so...
じゃあ　俺
東条さん　呼んでるから…。
おい　待てっ！
I said, wait!
You're the one who'll be waiting!
待つのはテメーだ！
観念するんだな！
You don't seem to get it!
（不良達）
ヘイ！ヘイ！ヘイ！ヘイ！
Sheesh...
《おいおい…》
《いくら何でも　これは…》
This might be a little much...
ヘイ！
Beat 'em to a pulp!
ぶちのめせ～！！
ヤーッ！！
うわぁ～っ！！
な　何だ？
≪どうした！？≫
≪何が起こった！？≫
What the...?
What's wrong?
What happened?
（邦枝）フッ…まったく…
笑わせるわねえ。→
Honestly... You make me laugh.
A single first year surrounded
by every student in the school?
たった１人の一年生を
全校生徒で囲んでおいて→
誇りだの　戦争だのと…→
And you call that a war of honor?!
恥を知りなさい！
Have you no shame?!
Kunieda!
邦枝！
≪邦枝！≫
≪烈怒帝瑠！≫
Kunieda!
Kunieda...
The Red Tails!
邦枝…。
お前…何で？
You? Why?
Go. I'll handle them here.
いきなさい。
ここは　私が引き受ける。
≪マジかよ…≫
≪クイーン≫
Seriously?
The Queen...
The Queen's got the Red Tails with her!
≪邦枝が　烈怒帝瑠を
連れてきやがった！≫
They're all siding with Oga?
≪こいつら全員
男鹿につく気かよ…≫
言っておくけど…→
I'll say this: Don't misunderstand me.
勘違いしないでよ。
あなたには借りがある。
I owe you one. That's all.
それだけだから！
Kunieda...
邦枝…。
（碇）キーキッキッキッ！→
邦枝ごときで
ガタついてんじゃねえよ。
Don't go cracking up just 'cause
Kunieda's bunch showed up!
Do your homework, brush your
teeth, and then start over again!
宿題やって　歯磨いてから
出直してきな！
The MK5 is here!
ｍｋ５登場！
The MK5!
≪ｍｋ５だ！≫
≪何だ　あのポーズは！！≫
≪ふざけてんのか！？≫
What's with the pose?
Are they screwing with us?
You're killing the mood!
≪空気読めよ　空気！≫
あ～　見ろよ　こっちにも！
Look, we've got another over here!
Who is it? I recognize him...
≪誰だ？見た顔だぞ≫
（下川）ナーイ！
Good night!
Aoi-chan, you look lovely in your Hakama...
葵ちゃん　袴姿もサイコー！
グッ！
Good...
ナィ…え？
...night?
Now that I think about it, we still
need to settle things, don't we?
（寧々）そういえば
アンタとの勝負は→
おあずけのままだったわね。
ち　ちょっと…
せめて葵ちゃんと戦わせて！
えいっ！！
Could I at least get to fight Aoi-chan?
Good night...!
（下川）グッナァ～イ！
You're bein' too friendly, Creepokawa.
なれなれしいのよ　キモ川。
キィーッ　キキキッ！
威勢がいいじゃねえか。
You're pretty strong.
But you don't think you'll be able to
beat us with something like that, right?
（嶋村）そんなもんで俺達に勝てる
つもりじゃねえだろな。
What was your name again?
Shimura or something?
しむらって言ったっけ？
あん？しまむらだ！
ShiMAmura!
Behind you.
後ろ。
あん？
おおっ！
うわっ！
（嶋村）よ　４丁拳銃！？
Quadruple pistols?!
うわ～っ！！
（碇）ダメだ　こりゃ～！
We suck!
Wiped Out Instantly
Wow.
すごいな…。
武器さえ使えれば
あの子達は負けないわ。
As long as they have their weapons,
those girls aren't losing to anyone.
Now, stand back.
さあ　下がって。
うん。
道をつくるわよ。
I will create a path.
おっ！
Shingetsu sword school.
（邦枝）心月流抜刀術…。
First style, reformed!
壱式　改　破山　菊一文字！
Mountain Shatter, Chrysanthemum Cut!
Chasing Flash!
追閃！
うわぁ～っ！！
（爆発音）
あっ…。
（東条）どうした？かおる。
What is it, Kaoru?
Yeah... There was just a strange explosion...
ああ　今　妙な爆発音が…。
爆発音？まだ火ぃつけてねえぞ。
Explosion?
But I ain't lit 'em yet.
No, not those.
いや　そっちじゃなくて…。
Man, what a shock!
（相沢）いやあ
びびった　びびった。→
こんな時間に　花火やるって
いうから来てみたら→
You said there were gonna be fireworks, so I
came around, but what's with the crowd so late?
何すか？あの人だかり。
Crowd?
（陣野）人だかり？
知らなかったんすか？
って　あっ！ちょっ…→
You didn't know?
W... B... Huh?
花火って　本物じゃないすか！
それ　一体どこで？
Fireworks? You meant real fireworks?!
And where did you get them?
I swiped 'em from my job at the festival.
ああ　祭りのバイトでくすねた。
That's a crime, you know.
（相沢）犯罪っすよ　それ。屈託ない
笑顔で　何言ってんすか～。
Stop grinning like a fool, damn you.
でけえ花火見りゃ　こいつも
ちっとは　元気出すと思ってよ。
I was thinkin' that if he saw some big
fireworks, it might cheer the little guy up.
それより庄次
人だかりっていうのは？
Anyway Shoji, what did you mean by a crowd?
I think, like, all the students are here.
全校生徒
集まってんじゃないかな。
They're tryin' to make a name for themselves
and become your followers, Tojo-san.
何か手柄たてて　東条さんの部下に
なるとか言って…。
Every student in the school?
（陣野）
全校生徒が？でたらめな話だ。
誰が言い出したんだ　そんなこと。
That's ridiculous. Who spread
that bogus story around?
Oh, that was me.
（東条）あ　それ　俺　俺。
（相沢・陣野）ええっ！？
It was you?
（陣野）って　あんたかい！
（東条）いや～　手下にしてくれとか
うるせえからさ～→
Well, they were all so annoying
trying to be my lackeys...
So I was like, "do a good job, and sure."
頑張ったらいいよ～つって。
（相沢）しかもテキトー。
And he wasn't hardly trying!
（東条）
まあ　いいじゃねえか。
どのみちウチは　そういう学校だ。
Why not? In the end, it's
how this school works.
Everyone gets together, fights,
全員集めてケンカして
最後まで立ってたヤツが大将。
and the one standing at the end is the boss.
What's wrong with that?
それでいいだろ。
派手にいこうじゃねえか。
Let's make a nice big boom...
With both fighting and fireworks...
ケンカも花火も…。
（ボン！）
はぁはぁ…。
（バン！）
（花火の音）
So, Oga Tatsumi... I've heard about you.
（東条）なあ　男鹿辰巳。
話は聞いたぜ。
お前　この赤ん坊の
親なんだってな。
You're this baby's parent, aren't you?
That explains why you
were unsettled back then.
どうりであの時
動揺していた訳だ。→
何故　言わなかった？
Why didn't you tell me?
Whatever. I'll give 'im back to you.
（東条）
まあ　いい。とにかく返すぜ。
俺は本気のお前と戦いてえんだ。→
I want to fight you for real.
Look, it's daddy!
ほ～れ　父ちゃんだぞ～。→
I don't wanna hear, "I went easy on you
'cause I was worried about my kid."
子供が心配で　力が出ねえなんて
言ってほしくねえからな。
Or maybe you'd fight even
stronger if you had to...
それとも　取り戻すために
戦う方が…。
...take him back?
あがるか？
フン　どっちもごめんだね。
Sorry, but neither.
I'm fighting for myself.
俺は　俺のために戦う。
第一そいつは　俺のガキじゃねえ。
In the first place, that ain't my kid.
Just like you, I've been caring
for him after picking him up.
てめえと同じで　拾ったから
預かってた。それだけだ。
That's all.
俺のとこに戻ってくるか
てめえに　ひっついてるか→
Whether he comes back to
me, or sticks to you...
それは…
こいつ自身が決めることだ。
That's...
...something he'll decide for himself.
あ…あ～　あ～っ。
Baby Beel...
ベル坊…。
ガーッ！！
はぁはぁ…。
ふ～　ふ～…。
Why, you...
てめえ！この…！
You...
Don't underestimate me!
ナメてんじゃねえぞ～！！
俺のために　リンクを切っただあ？
何様だ　コラァ！
You cut the link for my sake?!
Who asked you?!
Your tantrums...
てめえの
かんしゃくなんざなあ…。
...to me, they're no worse
than a static shock!
俺にとっちゃ…
豆電球とかわんねえんだよ！
ウォーッ！！
あ…。
き～っ！
ダ！
ベル坊…えっ！？
Baby Beel...
ダ！ダ！ダ！
えっ？おっ！うっ！！
ダァーッ！
（ラミア）
あは　完全に戻りましたね。
Looks like he's completely back to normal.
But that man... He opened Beelze-sama's
eyes just by calling out to him.
しかし　あの男
たった一声かけただけで→
ベルゼ様を目覚めさせるとは…→
He's really taken to him, I see...
本当に　なついておられるのだな。
アッ　アッ！
はしゃぐな！
Don't pull on me!
イーッ！
ん～っ！！
だぁ～っ！うるせえぞ　ベル坊！
離れろ！てめえ　ぶっとばすぞ！！
You're gettin' annoying, Baby Beel!
Let go! I'll kill you!
おい　コラ！
何やってんだ　ベル坊！
Hey, come on! What're you doing?
See? You're totally his parent.
（東条）
何だよ　やっぱりお前が
親なんじゃねえか。
そうか　ベル坊ってのか。
よかったな　このヤロー。
Ah, so his name is Baby Beel.
Good for him, the little bugger.
ダッ！
Now then, let's hurry and start this fight.
それじゃあ　とっとと
ケンカ始めようぜ。
I can hardly wait to fight you again.
（東条）また　てめえとやりたくて
ウズウズしてんだ。→
Put him down already, Oga.
さっさとそいつを下ろせ　男鹿。
ダッ。
ああ。
Yeah.
ハハハハ…。
Hey, come on! Tell me what happens next!
Huh?
I can't wait until next week!
Uh?
I wanna know so bad I can't sleep!
What does Count Poo intend to use
instead of a ball to play volleyball?
Oh, about that?!
Please, Oga!
Hurry and get your fight with Tojo over
with, so I can read the rest of Gohan-kun!
On the next Beelzebub: Who do you
think is Ishiyama's Strongest?
Alaindelon... My room, with you absent,
suddenly feels so big and roomy...
What the hell was that?